LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
A homicide disguised as an accident?
According to detectives, it is highly
probable that he was run over in such a way
that there would be critical damage
to his cybernetic cerebral core.
But the truck driver alleges that he was sleeping
at the wheel and doesn't remember anything...
Just to be sure,
we're scanning the driver's cyberbrain,
but we believe the results will be negative.
So we've lost our lead to the identity of the
man who threatened the Department of Energy.
Only if this man acted alone.
The subject's cybernetic body is
a Type 2902 by Toyoda Chemicals;
the cybernetic cerebral core
is a Type 2706-Kai by Derumo.
While these are older models,
they're brand new domestic ones.
The exterior is also a commercially available
standard model without any modifications.
The face alone is haute couture.
However, judging from the
deterioration of its cells,
it's most likely a holdover from the subject's
first transition to a cybernetic body.
That's an unusually piecemeal
assembly pattern for a criminal.
In addition, his methods were apparently shoddy.
It is possible that even the information
about a scandal at the DOE was a bluff.
And yet he died right before
he was about to be arrested,
in a manner similar to an assassination.
What is this symbol?
It appears to be the symbol representing the Shinjuku
ward, which was located in the former capital.
The one that sank below sea
level in the previous World War?
Yes. For some reason, this cyberbrain's
cerebral core is coated with glass and lead.
The symbol appears to have
been incised back then.
These are the man's possessions.
Among them is contact information for a reporter.
It should provide a chance
to learn this man's identity.
And this would be... a Marriage Ring?
Latent
Heat
Source
It's true that he contacted our
office and asked for a meeting.
Dobashi Fumiya Office
Reporter
I see.
It was a pretty fishy tip.
A public phone in Tokyo was
used to place the call...
Tokyo?
What about the tip itself?
It was about a scandal involving the DOE.
As if you guys have the time to
check out every hint of a scandal...
Well, we rarely meet with informants in person,
but he said he'd send in proof, so...
Just the two of you?
Smoking or non-smoking?
This way, please.
It's pitch black...
Yes, it was probably photographic
evidence of some kind,
but it's been completely exposed.
He probably thought digital
evidence wouldn't hold up in court.
There aren't many people who
can handle film these days.
Can I borrow this for a while?
That's fine with me,
but there's really nothing there.
Chief, it appears that the subject was in Tokyo,
at least up until a few days before he was killed.
He evidently mailed this exposed
film to the reporter from there.
All right.
Head straight to Tokyo.
While you're on your way, we'll figure out
which terminal was used for the phone call.
All by myself?
The rest of the team is continuing
to guard the Prime Minister.
I'll send one Tachikoma unit with you.
I wonder how bad the radiation's going to be...
How many years do you think it's
been since the last World War?
Residual radiation hasn't been detected since the
government disseminated the "Japanese Miracle."
Note: The Japanese Miracle is a swarm of micromachines capable of removing radiation from the environment
Roger.
New Tokyo.
This is New Tokyo station.
The train that just arrived is bound for Berutarube...
New Tokyo
Koushuu
Highway
Former Downtown District
If you're worried about residual
radiation, I suggest becoming a cyborg!
That's not it!
I just felt like it, that's all.
You don't feel well?
I can carry you in my pod!
I think that'll just make me get motion sickness.
Just shut up and follow me.
Hmph! What's THAT supposed to mean?!
So he called from this pay phone...
Have you seen this man?
Never seen him before.
He's supposed to have switched to a new
cybernetic body around here somewhere.
Who knows.
All the guys around here are trying to get by with
the minimum possible cybernetic functionality, so...
Let me have a look, too.
There have been a lot of missing people
lately, so I may know him.
It's this guy.
Let's see...
Oh, so you were talking about him.
You know him?
No, I don't.
But four or five days ago, on another damn
hot day like this, a guy all dressed up in
a black suit asked me about him, too.
He had a pretty vicious look to him.
Besides, a young lady was asking after the same
guy just a while ago in the gathering area.
So, what'd this pretty boy do, eh?
Nothing serious.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Do you know someone named Kotan Kanji?
Yeah, I do.
Really?
Yeah. Follow me.
I guess it's not easy to make
a find like that again...
Oh?
Where's Togusa-kun?
The string...
Uh-oh, I think it broke...
If you don't want to get hurt, get lost.
Y-You'll regret this!
Are you okay?
About the man who contacted the reporter:
We were able to confirm that there was indeed a man named
Kotan Kanji in the Kantou Residential Refugee Sector.
I see. Just to make sure, I showed the
woman the deceased's photo and ring.
She says they're Kotan's without a doubt.
Who is the woman?
Asagi Ruriko.
She was apparently with an NGO
that aided refugees two years ago,
and that's where she met Kotan.
They continued to keep in touch afterwards,
and had even promised to marry someday,
but all contact from Kotan ceased three months ago.
When a message from him suddenly
arrived a week ago telling her goodbye,
she left Akita prefecture and
came here to look for Kotan.
All right. Continue questioning that woman.
Roger.
Do you feel better now?
He died, didn't he? Kotan.
Kotan sent this to me.
He said he'd be able to leave
the refugee district soon, so...
But when he tried to get his ID,
Kotan's cybernetic body failed
the physical examination.
It didn't meet the minimum
functionality requirements.
When he found that out, he started to... avoid me.
He may have thought that I was trying
to hide the requirements from him.
Were you unable to reach him?
I contacted him several times...
I told him I'd help him get a new body...
He refused, though.
When he was found in Niihama,
he had already switched to a domestic model body.
Did you hear about that from him?
No, I didn't.
I see...
Actually, before he died, he was suspected
of blackmailing a government agency.
What...?
After hearing your story,
I thought Kotan might have been blackmailing
the agency in order to get a new body,
but he already had a new body, so...
Why did he attempt blackmail...
when he already had a new body?
Kotan had a difficult life,
but he wouldn't resort to crime!
Perhaps.
But his death may not have been an
accident; he may have been murdered.
What?
During the three months
that you two were estranged,
something happened to him.
Will you help me ask around in
the gathering area tomorrow?
Maybe it was about a month ago...
There was a rumour that someone was gathering up lots
of labourers whose bodies were completely cybernetic.
It was some juicy deal where
you could get a good body
for free if you were willing
to go within Inner Beltway 7.
For free?
Yep.
What's this about "Inner Beltway 7"?
It's a submerged area.
But since I haven't actually heard
of anyone who got a new body,
it might've just been a rumour, after all.
This man seems to have got a new body.
Hey, does anyone here know about that
deal where you could get a new body?
This man here apparently did get a new body.
Don't know him...
Hey!
I'm alive today thanks to Sensei.
Sensei?
Yeah.
He taught me a lot of things
within Inner Beltway 7.
What happened there?
I don't really know, either.
I was just working,
doing whatever I was told to do.
Do you remember who your employer was?
I think it was Kuromatsu
Electrics or something like that.
It was to excavate a facility
that got buried during the War.
Kuromatsu Electrics, Inc.
We needed to go deep underground.
so they told us to come after our
bodies became completely cybernetic.
I'd initially given up because the minimum requirement
was to have a body that was 98% cybernetic.
But a back-alley doctor fudged the
percentage for me, and I was able to get in.
Did those bodies have this symbol?
Yeah, everyone's did.
Sensei was really glad that he got his new body...
even though no one can be 100% sure that
they've received a totally new body,
since you can't see your own
cybernetic cerebral core.
In the end, about forty labourers were rounded up,
and went deep underground.
There were others who were
fudging their percentage, too.
So, I teamed up with Sensei and began working.
If I remember correctly,
it was called "Nekkou," or something like that...
We had anti-dust masks on, but even so
our nostrils would still get pitch black.
Sensei said that it would be fine if
we deactivated our sensory organs...
but I said that wasn't possible for me,
since I didn't have a fully cybernetic body.
Then, he got this really scary look on his face,
and said that I'd die unless
I got out of there right then.
But... I wanted money badly, so I didn't listen.
That's why he gave me this, and told me
to get the hell out if it turned black.
And then, four days after we started
working, something big happened.
Sirens suddenly sounded...
We were wondering what the hell was going on,
when a bunch of guys who looked like
engineers were carried out on stretchers.
I finally realised how dangerous this job was then.
That's when you ran?
Yeah.
Before we knew it,
guys dressed all in black had arrived.
The two of us were able to make it out of there...
but when I glanced back on my way out,
the ones who were with us had got
trapped behind a huge steel door.
What did Kotan do after that?
He said something about having to make
what he saw back in the tunnels public...
and went away somewhere...
Can you guide us to that Inner Beltway 7 area?
No way!
I'll never go back there, even if you pay me!
It can just be for part of the way.
Please!
I want to know what Kotan saw there, too!
The GSDF is here.
When I ran out of there, that fence wasn't there.
If you go in here, you should be able to
reach the place where it all happened.
Sorry, but this is as far as I'll go.
That's okay. Thanks.
No Unauthorised Personnel Beyond this Point.
Protective gear and film badge required at all times. Evacuate immediately if readings are elevated.
Tokyo Nuclear
This is...
Armour Suits!
Dammit!
Jump!
Hurry!
Hurry!!!
Are you all right, Togusa-kun?
Tachikoma!
Ta-dah!
Note: This is the Tokyo Metropolitan City Hall
The arriving train is bound
for New Fukuoka, Mirai 52.
Kotan must've decided to work there so he could
be with you, even though he knew it was dangerous.
Since he happened to be knowledgeable enough
to figure out what the facility was...
he was killed.
I'll come back for his body after going home.
All right.
Let me know immediately if anything happens.
Yes.
Headline: Niihama Newspaper
Kuromatsu Electrics' President Commits Suicide
Collusion With Foreigners Suspected
Kotan witnessed an accident in the hidden,
deep subterranean nuclear power plant.
He used that to blackmail the DOE...
but it could be that he tried
to make the scandal public.
I see.
Judging from what you've told me,
it seems a criticality accident occurred during an
operation and the facility was hastily buried,
but the military does not seem aware of this event.
The real question is, under whose jurisdiction and for
what purpose was this pre-World War relic being excavated?
Those black-suited men...
I think there is still more to this.
Write a report as soon as you get back.
Roger.
Headline: Labourer accidentally dismantled.
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
and singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
(the time is now)
All the truth,
(All the truth)
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.